<resources>
    <string name="app_name">App</string>

    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>

    <!--Used for PHQ9_Quiz.java as a Question index display-->
    <string name="question_index_display">Question %1$d</string>

    <!--Clinic: ...\n
        Location: ...\n
        Phone number: ...\n
        Email: ..."-->
    <string name="psychiatrist_info_edit">Clinic: %1$s\nLocation: %2$s\nPhone number: %3$s\nEmail: %4$s</string>


    <!--Diagnosis result-->
    <string name="diagnosis_result_none">Depression Free</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_minimum">Minimum or None</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_mild">Mild Depression</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_moderate">Moderate Depression</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_moderately_severe">Moderately Severe</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_severe">Severe Depression</string>

    <!--Diagnosis conclusion-->
    <string name="diagnosis_result_none_conclusion">Your answers suggest you may not be suffering from depression.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_mild_conclusion">Your answers suggest you may be suffering from mild depression.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_moderate_conclusion">Your answers suggest you are suffering from moderate depression.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_moderately_severe_conclusion">Your answers suggest you are suffering from moderate to severe depression.</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_severe_conclusion">Your answers suggest you are suffering from severe depression.</string>

    <!--Diagnosis advice-->
    <string name="diagnosis_result_low_priority_advice">Still if you feel something isn’t quite right we recommend you schedule an appointment with a doctor. If you need help finding a mental health professional we suggest to reach out in our Psychiatrist section</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_mid_priority_advice">Consider watchful waiting, and testing again normally within two weeks. We additionally suggest it would be prudent to start a conversation with a doctor. If you need help finding a mental health professional we suggest to reach out in our Psychiatrist section</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_mid_high_priority_advice">It doesn’t necessarily mean you have depression but is important that you schedule an appointment with your doctor or a mental health worker. If you need help finding a mental health professional we suggest to reach out in our Psychiatrist section</string>
    <string name="diagnosis_result_high_priority_advice">It is important that you schedule an appointment with your doctor or a mental health worker. If you need help finding a mental health professional we suggest to reach out in our Psychiatrist section</string>

</resources>